Search

Donate

ABOUT

#### [About PERC](https://www.perc.org/about/)

OUR FOCUS

#### [Our Focus](https://www.perc.org/our-focus/)

RESEARCH

#### [All Research](https://www.perc.org/research)

Search

Search

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us, and so we’ve prepared this document to explain what data we gather, how we use it, and how we strive to protect it. This privacy policy applies specifically to perc.org.

Personal identification information
-----------------------------------

We may collect personal identification information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our Site, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available to you on our Site. You may be asked for identifying information such as name, email address, or mailing address. You certainly do not have to provide that information, and can browse our Site anonymously. But providing it helps us to keep you informed about our work, and helps us make sure our website is relevant and useful to you. Occasionally we may require that you provide a name, email or mailing address to access reports or other proprietary information.

Non-personal identification information
---------------------------------------

We collect non-personal identification information about those who interact with our Site, such as their browser name, the type of computer and technical information they are using to connect to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information. This data is aggregated and used to help us make our Site stable and usable to all visitors.

Web browser cookies
-------------------

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and to store your preferences. Cookies can be helpful in customizing your website visit, and in helping us understand what types of information are most useful to our Site visitors. You always have the choice to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to provide an alert when cookies are being sent. If you do so, some parts of our Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information
--------------------------------

We use the personal information we collect to:

* Run and operate a website that is useful and relevant
* Display content on the Site correctly
* Run a promotion, contest, survey or other website feature
* Send you information about topics you have told us you care about
* Update you on the impact of PERC via regular emails (which you will always have the option to unsubscribe from)
* Respond to inquiries about our Site or programs

How we protect your information
-------------------------------

We follow data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures designed to protect your information against unauthorized access or uses.

Sharing your personal information
---------------------------------

We may selectively share our contact lists with like-minded allies who we think have information you would want to see. However, you can always request that your information not be shared with anyone by calling us at 406-587-9591 or emailing us at [perc@perc.org](mailto:perc@perc.org). We also may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Changes to this privacy policy
------------------------------

PERC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site.

Contacting us
-------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at [perc@perc.org](mailto:perc@perc.org).

### Because incentives matter  
for conservation.

2048 Analysis Dr Ste A  
Bozeman, MT 59718

406-587-9591

##### Join 10,000+ people who receive timely news and views.

Email address(Required)

Comments

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

© Property and Environment Research Center | [Privacy Policy](https://www.perc.org/privacy-policy/)
